{
    "subject": "resource/David_Burtka",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "Dearborn, Michigan, United States",
    "human_readable": "David Burtka was born in Dearborn, Michigan, United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9159097075462341,
            "question": "Where was David Burtka born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9074150919914246,
            "question": "What state was David Burtka born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665851354598999,
            "question": "In which country was David Burtka born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7042064070701599,
            "question": "What is the name of David Burtka's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557481288909912,
            "question": "What information can you tell me about David Burtka's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6238200664520264,
            "question": "Can you give me more details about Dearborn, Michigan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5761462450027466,
            "question": "Is Dearborn a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5725317597389221,
            "question": "Where might David Burtka have grown up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4148394465446472,
            "question": "Is there anything else known about David Burtka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37172237038612366,
            "question": "What are some notable places or things associated with Dearborn?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Burtka was born in Dearborn, Michigan, United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1919_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else known about David Burtka?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1919_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might David Burtka have grown up?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1919_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Dearborn a city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1919_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1919_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that David Burtka was indeed born in Dearborn, Michigan. This information is mentioned in multiple documents, including files 1.txt, 46.txt, and others. Therefore, the output value is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the context information provided, which mentions that \"David Michael Burtka was born in Dearborn, Michigan on May 29, 1975\" and \"David Burtka was born on 29 May 1975 in Dearborn, Michigan, USA,\" confirming his birthplace as Dearborn, Michigan, United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}